Preliminary guide to the Karren Alenier literary papers, 1962 - 2016 MS2223
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Publicity and marketing, Series 6
  - Play bills, undated; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Play bills, undated; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Play bills, undated; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Play bills, undated; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Play bills, undated; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Play bills, programs, undated; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Play bills, programs, undated; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Programs, news letters, undated; Series 6 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Programs, playbills, undated; Series 6 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Readings, undated; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Stage bills, undated; Series 6 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Stage bills, undated; Series 6 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Stage bills, undated; Series 6 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Stage bills, undated; Series 6 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Stage bills, undated; Series 6 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Stagebills, undated; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Audiovisual and digital files, 2005-2007; Series 7
  Arranged alphabetically by media type.
  - Cassette tape: Anthony Tommasini interview, undated; Series 7 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Cassette tape: Eve Gigliotti, 2006 May 11; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Cassette tape: Hans Callas, undated; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Cassette tape: J.D. McClatchy, 2005 August 04; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Cassette tape: John Yoffe, 2006 May 11; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Cassette tape: Libby Larsen interview, 2004 February 24; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Cassette tape: Nancy Rhodes, 2006 April; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Cassette tape: Ned Roren, undated; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Cassette tape: Squonch Opera, undated; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Cassette tape: Tim Page interview, undated; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Cassette tape:Renate Stondal and Karren Alenier, 2004 August 16; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - CD: DC places, undated; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - CD: Raconteurs reading, undated; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - DVD: Gertrude Stein, roundtable discussion, undated; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Floppy disks, undated; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Floppy disks, undated; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - VHS tape: Poet as Power Broker, 2007; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 14)